<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xmlns:rng="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"
 xml:lang="en">
 <teiHeader>
  <fileDesc>
   <titleStmt>
    <title>TEI customization DiXiT workshop Athens</title>
    <author>Elena Spadini</author>
   </titleStmt>
   <publicationStmt>
    <publisher>TEI Consortium</publisher>
    <availability status="free">
     <p>TEI material can be licensed differently depending on the use you intend to make of it.
      Hence it is made available under both the CC+BY and BSD-2 licences. The CC+BY licence is
      generally appropriate for usages which treat TEI content as data or documentation. The BSD-2
      licence is generally appropriate for usage of TEI content in a software environment. For
      further information or clarification, please contact the TEI Consortium (info@tei-c.org).</p>
    </availability>
   </publicationStmt>
   <notesStmt>
    <note type="ns">http://www.example.org/ns/nonTEI</note>
   </notesStmt>
   <sourceDesc>
    <p>Written from scratch.</p>
   </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
 </teiHeader>
 <text>
  <body>
   <head>TEI Complete</head>
   <p> of the TEI (P5) modules. This is a very useful starting place for manually creating your own
    customizations — it is much easier to delete the modules you do not want than to add the modules
    you do. Furthermore this customization often proves helpful for testing TEI software.This TEI
    customization is intended for educational purposes for the DiXiT Workshop 'Scholarly Digital
    Editions and Modern Greek Studies' held in Athens, 24-28 April.This TEI customization is
    intended for educational purposes for the DiXiT Workshop 'Scholarly Digital Editions and Modern
    Greek Studies' held in Athens, 24-28 April.</p>
   <p>However, this particular TEI customization is <emph>not recommended</emph> for actual use for
    encoding documents. It produces schemas and reference documentation that will be much larger,
    and include many more elements, than almost anyone could conceivably ever need. Tempting though
    it may be simply to have absolutely everything, and <q>just ignore</q> elements not required,
    experience has shown that their presence makes the documentation harder to read and use, and
    makes a schema that is far more lax than desired.</p>
   <schemaSpec ident="tei_dixit" start="TEI teiCorpus" prefix="">
    <moduleRef key="tei"/>
    <!-- required -->
    <moduleRef key="core"/>
    <!-- required -->
    <moduleRef key="analysis"/>
    <moduleRef key="certainty"/>
    <moduleRef key="corpus"/>
    <moduleRef key="dictionaries"/>
    <moduleRef key="drama"/>
    <moduleRef key="header"/>
    <!-- required -->
    <moduleRef key="linking"/>
    <moduleRef key="msdescription"/>
    <moduleRef key="namesdates"/>
    <moduleRef key="textstructure"/>
    <!-- required -->
    <moduleRef key="transcr"/>
    <moduleRef key="verse"/>
    <moduleRef key="tagdocs"/>
   </schemaSpec>
  </body>
 </text>
</TEI>
